<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' standalone='yes'?>
<xml>
  <top>
    <num>1</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about a powerful New York crime family.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>2</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about a professional thief and a seasoned cop in Los Angeles.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>3</num> 
    <title>A crime movie involving a hunter finding a briefcase full of money in Texas.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>4</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about tracking down the Zodiac Killer in San Francisco.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>5</num> 
    <title>A crime movie featuring Los Angeles mobsters and a mysterious briefcase.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>6</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about a Harlem drug kingpin smuggling heroin.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>7</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about an undercover cop and a mole in an Irish gang in Boston.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>8</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about two detectives and a serial killer inspired by the seven deadly sins.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>9</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about police investigating murders in 1950s Los Angeles.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>10</num> 
    <title>A crime movie about a man's wife going missing and the ensuing media circus.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>11</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about a Scottish warrior's fight against the King of England.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>12</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about Oskar Schindler saving Polish-Jewish refugees during WWII.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>13</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about a Roman general seeking revenge in the gladiatorial arenas.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>14</num> 
    <title>A historical movie focusing on President Abraham Lincoln's efforts to abolish slavery.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>15</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about the rivalry between Mozart and Salieri in the Austrian court.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>16</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about the life of the last Emperor of China.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>17</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about a Nobel Laureate economist struggling with schizophrenia.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>18</num> 
    <title>A historical movie dramatizing the Trojan War inspired by Homer’s "The Iliad".</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>19</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about King George VI overcoming his stammer during WWII.</title>
  </top>
  <top>
    <num>20</num> 
    <title>A historical movie about the Rwandan genocide and a hotel manager's heroic acts.</title>
  </top>
</xml>
"""
